<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deployment on fabio - The Consul Load-Balancer</title>
    <link>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deployment on fabio - The Consul Load-Balancer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fabiolb.net/deploy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Direct</title>
      <link>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/direct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/direct/</guid>
      <description>In the following setup fabio is configured to listen on the public ip(s) where it can optionally terminate SSL traffic for one or more domains - one ip per domain.
To scale fabio you can deploy it together with the frontend services which provides high-availability and distributes the network bandwidth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind existing Gateway</title>
      <link>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/existing-lb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/existing-lb/</guid>
      <description>In the following setup fabio is configured receive all incoming traffic from an existing gateway which also terminates SSL for one or more domains.
Again, to scale fabio you can deploy it together with the frontend services which provides high-availability and distributes the network bandwidth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon ELB</title>
      <link>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/amazon-elb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/amazon-elb/</guid>
      <description>You can deploy fabio behind an Amazon ELB and enable PROXY protocol support to get the remote address and port of the client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon API Gateway</title>
      <link>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/amazon-api-gw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabiolb.net/deploy/amazon-api-gw/</guid>
      <description>You can deploy fabio as the target of an Amazon API Gateway.
or behind an ELB with PROXY protocol support:
You can authenticate calls from the API Gateway with a client certificate. This requires that you configure an HTTPS listener on fabio with a valid certificate.
To enable fabio to validate the Amazon generated certificate you need to configure the aws.apigw.cert.cn as follows:
proxy.addr = 1.2.3.4:9999;your/cert.pem;your/key.pem;api-gw-cert.pem aws.apigw.cert.cn = ApiGateway  api-gw-cert.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>